sproinggames.com 2016-06-17

# Privacy Policy - Sproing

Effective, February 27th, 2015

This Privacy Policy governs your use of sproing.com and all the services that sproing.com offers on the sproing.com website including the games and applications offered by Sproing Interactive Media GmbH (Sproing) and accessed through third party web sites.

 **Privacy**  
Sproing respects the privacy of visitors to our website and our applications. Any information collected is subject to the pertinent social network’s policy. By playing the game, you may be granting your social network permission to share your e-mail address and any other personally identifiable information with Sproing. If you do not agree, then you should not play Sproing games or submit any personally identifiable information through them.

 **Cookies**  
Cookies are little text files placed on your computer to save game date like sound settings. The game might send cookies to your computer when you access or view content. You can disable cookies at any time but your settings will not be persistent then.

 **Logfiles**  
When you access our games data is generated which is stored for the purpose to obtain technical and statistical information to improve the games.

 **Third Party Sites**  
Sproing-Sites may contain links to third-party websites that are not owned or controlled by Sproing. Sproing has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party websites. In addition, Sproing will not and cannot censor or edit the content of any third-party site. By using the Sproing-Sites, you expressly relieve Sproing from any and all liability arising from your use of any third-party website.

 **Modification of Privacy Policy**  
Sproing reserves the right to change or modify the Privacy Policy at any time. We will attempt to give you advance notice of any substantive changes, but reserve the right to make such modifications immediately if required. If you use Sproing Services after any of such changes become effective you are accepting the new Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, do not use or access (or continue to use or access) the Services. It is your responsibility to check if there have been changes to these Privacy Policy and to review such changes.

We are committed to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. If you have any questions about these Privacy Policy, please contact Sproing at [office@sproing.com](mailto:office@sproing.com).
